San Carlos de Bariloche – Rio Negro, Argentina

# **Agustin Mandarini**

# **Full Stack Developer**

agustinmandarini47@gmail.com

Portfolio: <a href="https://portfolio-agustin-mandarini.vercel.app/">https://portfolio-agustin-mandarini.vercel.app/</a>

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/agustin-mandarini-8a73a4225/

GitHub: https://github.com/AgustinMandarini

Tel.: +54 9 11 39534746

Location: San Carlos de Bariloche – Rio Negro, Argentina

My expertise is as a fullstack developer with a background in network systems for electronic security. I have experience in both Frontend and Backend development. I enjoy working collaboratively within a team. I take pleasure in providing support and being a resource for my team, as well as requesting assistance when I deem it necessary. Throughout my experience, I have successfully completed projects that had a positive impact on the professional development of the team and on the company's value. Additionally, I have knowledge in agile methodologies, SCRUM, GIT, data structures, algorithms, Python, Django, Javascript, Node.js, Express, Sequelize, Docker, Postgres, React, Redux, HTML, and CSS frameworks.

English Level: C2 Proficient.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Python Developer | Baldor SRL

May 2022 to Present

Designed applications for sound level measuring machines for safety and hygiene purposes. The systems were entirely developed in Python.

- Increased product sales by enhancing the performance and user-friendliness of the applications.
- Enhanced the visual appeal of the UI.
- Integrated libraries such as matplotlib and pdftohtml to generate styled reports.
- Designed a communication protocol to establish connections and facilitate data retrieval from the equipment.

**GitHub:** <a href="https://github.com/AgustinMandarini/Vibrac">https://github.com/AgustinMandarini/Vibrac</a> **Baldor SRL:** <a href="https://www.baldorshop.com.ar/">https://www.baldorshop.com.ar/</a>

Fullstack Web Developer - MSC Amobiamientos

Aug 2023 to Nov 2023

Developed an dynamic E-Commerce platform for a furniture and furnishings startup, showcasing expertise in JavaScript, React, and Node.is.

- Implemented a secure user authentication system utilizing JWT and Auth0, enhancing the application's data security and user privacy.
- Designed and deployed an efficient admin dashboard with CRUD functionality for users, products, and sales, providing seamless management capabilities.
- Installed and configured Cloudinary for image storage, optimizing performance and reliability in handling multimedia content.
- Coordinated a team of 8 developers to efficiently organize and execute frontend and backend development tasks, ensuring timely project delivery and client satisfaction.
- Deployed the platform on Vercel and Render, ensuring optimal performance and scalability.

**Frontend:** React, Redux, Bootstrap 4. **Backend**: Node, Express y Sequelize **Database**: PostgreSQL y Sequelize.

Link: https://msc-amoblamientos.vercel.app/home

**GitHub:** <a href="https://github.com/AgustinMandarini/MSC-Amoblamientos">https://github.com/AgustinMandarini/MSC-Amoblamientos</a>

# **Full Stack Teaching Assistant**

Aug 2023 to Present

Academic experience - Henry Bootcamp

- Coordinated a group of students to facilitate their integration into the study team.
- Assisted in solving exercises and encouraged group collaboration (Pair Programming).
- Proposed ideas for improving Bootcamp processes.

# Electronic Security and Telecommunications Specialist | Argentinian Army

Sep 2015 to Present

- Designed electrical and telecommunications network infrastructure.
- Planned and designed electronic security systems, including the placement of devices, cameras, alarms, vibration sensors, etc.
- Coordinated installation and technical teams.
- Provided advisory and consultancy services to clients for electronic security solutions in sensitive sectors
  of the Argentinian Army.
- Configured and maintained equipment, software, and networks.

#### **PROJECTS**

# Full Stack Web Developer - Doggypedia App

Jun 2023 to Aug 2023

Academic experience - Henry Bootcamp

Developed a Single Page Application (SPA) that consumes an API and displays information about 264 different dog breeds, allowing users to create and save new breeds in a database, search for them by name, and filter them.

Frontend: React

**Backend:** Express y Sequelize **Database:** PostgreSQL y Sequelize. **Link:** <a href="https://doggypedia-nu.vercel.app/">https://doggypedia-nu.vercel.app/</a>

GitHub: https://github.com/AgustinMandarini/dogsApp

## **TECHNOLOGIES:**

**Programming languages:** Javascript, Node, Python, HTML, CSS. **Frameworks:** React, Redux, Express. **Databases:** Sequelize, Postgres. **Deployment & Hosting:** Vercel, Render, Railway.**Tools:** Git, Slack, Docker. **Agile:** Scrum.

#### PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

- Completed a comprehensive Full Stack Web Developer program at Henry Bootcamp, consisting of 800 hours of theoretical and practical coursework.
- Industrial Engineering from Universidad Nacional General Sarmiento, 2011 to 2014.

#### ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

- AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials, 2023
- CS50's Web Programming with Python and Javascript
- CS50x: Introduction to Computer Science, Jul to Nov 2021

# **LANGUAGES**

- Spanish: Native Speaker.
- English: C2 Proficient https://www.efset.org/cert/GxHGvZ